We found no virus
我们没有发现病毒
Don't worry
不用担心
Let's go back first
我们先回去吧
OK
好的
Are you OK?
你好吗？
The source of the virus has been found
病毒源头已找到
and delete
和删除
Firewall has been fixed
防火墙已修复
Thank you so much
非常感谢
but
但
this time
这次
The local network’s firewall is compromised
本地网络的防火墙被攻击
It is implemented via an internal computer
它是通过内部计算机实现的
you mean
你的意思是
Internal staff problems
内部员工有问题
maybe someone
也许有人
Remove the virus-contained USB flash drive
取出带有病毒的U盘
to internal computer
到内部计算机
System attack.
系统攻击。
we will check carefully
我们会仔细检查
If it were so clear
如果这么清楚的话
Maybe it's just the music this time
也许这次只是音乐
Please strengthen management
请加强管理
Especially the cybersecurity department
尤其是网络安全部门
Must be upgraded regularly
必须定期升级
firewall system
防火墙系统
be defensive
做好防守
We will strengthen management
我们将加强管理
OK
好的
We'll come back now
我们现在就回来
thank you all
谢谢你们
i have something
我有东西
Are you leaving tonight?
今晚你要离开吗？
According to the plan
按照计划
And you
你呢
Yaoyao goes to see Chu Zhiyi
瑶瑶去见楚执一
waiting for news from her
等待她的消息
Can I see you again?
我可以再见到你吗？
if there is a chance
如果有机会的话
I will find contact information
我会找到联系方式
give yourself to me
把你自己交给我
The same to you
你也是
Come on, put it on
来吧，穿上它
suits you
适合你
before i leave
在我离开前
I have no chance to go home
我已经没有机会回家了
This is good
这很好
I have no idea
我不知道
How should I say goodbye to my uncle?
我该如何和叔叔说再见呢？
so hot
好帅啊
Is it going well there?
那里进展顺利吗？
Yes
是的
As I expected
正如我之前所预料的
I will leave Huang Zicheng to you
我就把黄子诚留给你了
i can't control it
我无法控制它
He listens to you more
他更听你说话
Don't worry I have a plan
别担心我有计划
I'm not worried about you
我不担心你
I'm very worried about Mr. Zhang
我很担心张先生
you will come back alive
你会活着回来
i will try my best
我会尽力而为
this event
此次事件
Very bad
很坏
this happened
这发生过
This means that the entire technology sector
这意味着整个技术部门
In the technical department
在技​​术部
Adjutant Wang
王副官
. My fault
。我的错
although
尽管
we have made a choice
我们已经做出了选择
for firewall
用于防火墙
Comprehensive inspection
全面检查
but it appeared
但它出现了
these errors
这些错误
my job is not good
我的工作不好
all of them
他们全部
Half-year bonus will be deducted
半年奖金将被扣除
I won't let
我不会让
It won't happen again
不会再发生了
If something like this happens again
如果再发生类似的事情
it won't
它不会
It's that simple to deal with
处理起来就是这么简单
Understood
明白了
Vice President
副总裁
What do you have to say?
你有什么要说的？
I believe
我相信
Your punishment is light
你的处罚很轻
Online data security is extremely important
在线数据安全极其重要
any small mistake
任何一个小错误
may cause huge losses
可能会造成巨大损失
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
what should I do?
我应该怎么办？
I believe
我相信
Someone has to be responsible for this
这件事必须有人负责
Vice President of Hospital
医院副院长
The manager has decided
经理已经决定了
like i said
就像我说的
Who should be responsible for this matter?
这件事情应该由谁负责呢？
nature
自然
Of course it is me
当然是我
I have to take responsibility for this
我必须为此负责
Not long ago I suggested
不久前我建议
in order to make improvements
为了做出改进
Comprehensive upgrade
全面升级
then
当时
I did not find it
我没有找到
System problems
系统问题
in system system
在系统系统中
So I asked the deputy director
所以我问副主任
punish me severely
严惩我
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
How should I punish you?
我该怎么惩罚你呢？
Of course I'd be fired
我当然会被解雇
But for
但对于
To avoid unnecessary problems
以免出现不必要的问题
I wrote a resignation letter
我写了辞职信
Send to manager's email address
发送至经理的电子邮件地址
thank you all
谢谢你们
For your long-term care
为了您长久以来的呵护
this
这
Hello
你好
I got my stuff
我拿到了我的东西
But it seems like someone is following me
但好像有人在跟踪我
you were discovered
你被发现了
My colleague last time
上次我同事
she doubts me
她怀疑我
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
I'll get rid of her first, then I'll find you
我先摆脱她，然后去找你
OK
好的
say something embarrassing
说一些尴尬的话
I want to hear what you say
我想听听你说什么
wait for me to say
等我说
Your skills are very good, waiting for your reply
你的技术很好，等待回复
i made a mistake
我犯了错误
shouldn't be
不应该是
I don't think about the consequences
我不考虑后果
Definitely not
一定不
Disobey the company commander's orders
不服从连长命令
You shouldn't quit as soon as you get to the top
你不应该一爬到顶峰就辞职
You're so beautiful
你太美了
I heard you are very strong
听说你很强
in front of everyone
在所有人面前
Then I quit
然后我就退出了
Not if you make a mistake
如果你犯了错误就不会
you must take responsibility
你必须承担责任
You are wrong
您错了
Did you create the virus?
病毒是你创造的吗？
no no
不，不
Am I an unreliable person?
我是一个不靠谱的人吗？
You and your brother are recently
你和你弟弟最近
recently?
最近？
what can we do?
我们可以做什么？
Do not you trust me?
你不相信我吗？
Don't you believe him?
你不相信他吗？
therefore
因此
I will tell the staff
我会告诉工作人员
write a report
写报告
Then you stay at work and check
然后你留在工作岗位检查
no no no
不不不
Laohuang Laohuang
老黄 老黄
Lao Huang, give it to me
老黄给我
I resign
我辞职
I'm not reckless
我并没有鲁莽
look
看
I work here
我在这儿上班
months ago
几个月前
I find
我发现
I can not
我不能
at this place
在这个地方
To realize my lofty ambitions
为了实现我远大的抱负
please tell me
请告诉我
he can let you
他可以让你
use your wisdom
发挥你的智慧
let's go
我们走吧
A place with great ambitions
一个有远大抱负的地方
I found it
我找到了
Where?
在哪里？
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
What do you think about joining Duane?
您对加入杜安有什么看法
Do not talk to me
不要跟我说话
look
看
Why you ask yourself?
你为什么问自己？
Did you finish it?
你做完了吗？
Do not you trust me?
你不相信我吗？
Zicheng
子成
I have grown up now
我现在已经长大了
I am very lazy
我很懒
I don't want to care about her
我不想关心她
but humans
但人类
you must be responsible
你必须负责
when i came to the company
当我来到公司的时候
When I come to the company to work
当我来公司上班的时候
I told you
我告诉你了
you have to think carefully
你必须仔细思考
but now
但现在
no explanation
没有解释
You want to resign without reason
你想无故辞职
How can I trust you?
我怎么能相信你呢？
I resigned
我辞职了
what are you saying? speak loudly.
你在说什么？大声说。
I said
我说
you are right
你是对的
I
我
future
将来
i want you to be
我希望你成为
responsible
负责任的
Outstanding contemporary youth
当代优秀青年
as you like
随你便
I believe
我相信
You should go back to the game company
你还是回游戏公司吧
keep playing
继续玩
Anyway, you can't do anything else for long periods of time
无论如何，你不能长时间做任何其他事情
my dad
我的爸爸
I recently
我最近
stay outside for a while
到外面待一会儿
Why did you go abroad again?
怎么又出国了？
Where to go?
去哪里？
with whom
和谁一起
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
her family is there
她的家人在那里
I will stay with her
我会陪着她
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
Have you two reconciled?
你们两个和好了吗？
Yes
是的
to visit her parents
去看望她的父母
Why are you so stubborn?
你为什么这么固执？
just to meet your family
只是为了见见你的家人
What exactly do you mean?
你到底是什么意思？
I'm not afraid that you're not young
我不怕你不年轻
Yes or no
是不是
I'll break it with my hands
我会用手打破它
it's not easy
这并不容易
someone loves you
有人爱你
Why didn't she send you here earlier?
她为什么不早点送你来？
All right
好吧
i will listen to you
我会听你的
correct
正确的
But I must remind you
但我必须提醒你
You must check your health
你必须检查你的健康状况
Hospital
医院
Didn't the doctor ask you to re-examine?
医生没有让你重新检查吗？
I remember these days
我记得这些天
All right
好吧
You talk more than your mother
你比你妈妈更爱说话
If my mother were here
如果我妈妈在的话
traveling abroad
出国旅行
Is there enough money?
钱够吗？
Yes
是的
OK, let's go
好，出发
I have a meeting soon
我很快就要开会
I gotta go
我要走了
give yourself to me
把你自己交给我
let's go
我们走吧
I will really go
我真的会去
what i told you
我告诉你的话
i must listen
我必须听
Understood
明白了
Enter
进入
Have you considered
你想好了吗
sorry
对不起
I can't stand it
我受不了
he rejected me
他拒绝了我
I can't connect
我无法连接
in fact
事实上
He doesn't like me very much
他不太喜欢我
He already suspected
他已经怀疑了
Said I betrayed him
说我背叛了他
She started warning me everywhere
她开始到处警告我
What's this?
这是什么？
Open it
打开它
This is for you
这是给您的
Why did you give me this?
你为什么给我这个？
Since Huang Ziqing
自从黄自清
He doubts you
他怀疑你
Use this to protect yourself
拿这个来保护自己
Can you use it?
你能用吗？
Yes
是的
But I've never used it before
但我以前从未使用过它
accept it and be done with it
接受并完成它
your last mission
你的最后一个任务
if someone blocks you
如果有人阻止你
i will kill him
我会杀他
Is this you
这是你吗
The road to the free world
通往自由世界的道路
your destiny
你的命运
under your control
在你的掌控之下
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
Where is the tail?
尾巴在哪里？
Already eliminated
已经被淘汰了
Where is the thing?
东西在哪里？
you do not trust me
你不信任我
Now I only believe in myself
现在我只相信我自己
someone who will help you
会帮助你的人
When will he arrive?
他什么时候到？
I won't stay here long
我不会在这里久留
Guoan now suspects you
国安现在怀疑你了
Give me the card
把卡给我
I'm going to get something
我去拿东西
Even if they doubt you
即使他们怀疑你
They can't get the evidence
他们拿不到证据
you can continue your work
你可以继续你的工作
this is your opinion
这是你的意见
Or Mr. Yu’s opinion
或者于先生的意见
Does it matter?
这重要吗？
nature
自然
He promised me I would come out
他答应我我会出来
I won't stay here
我不会留在这里
He got the job done for him
他替他完成了工作
You can get more rewards
你可以获得更多奖励
go out
出去
It's no safer than staying in Gimhae
并不比留在金海更安全
Believe me
相信我
stay here
待在这
will be more valuable
将会更有价值
i will stay
我会留下来
I will remain under your control
我将继续受你控制
Sooner or later it will be revealed
迟早会被揭晓
The National Security Bureau only suspects
国安局只怀疑
when they find anything
当他们发现任何事情时
I won't be able to leave
我将无法离开
I received a message from Mr. Zhang
我收到张先生的消息
"Gao Tianyang"
“高天阳”
He insisted on leaving with her
他坚持要和她一起离开
Have you ever thought about it?
你有没有想过？
from start to finish
从开始到结束
this is a trap
这是一个陷阱
one move
一招
One of them became Gao Tianyang
其中之一成就了高天阳
In the trap of our hearts
在我们内心的陷阱里
Is this a trap?
这到底是不是陷阱
Gao Tianyang leaves the National Security Bureau
高天阳离开国安局
for us
为了我们
no use to us
对我们来说没有用
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I think
我认为
If you give the card to the National Security Bureau
如果你把卡给国安
I plead guilty
我认罪
How many years will be reduced from the sentence?
刑期会减多少年？
you won't do that
你不会那样做
When you killed Xiao Yi
当你杀了萧毅的时候
I thought there would be a day like this
我以为会有这样的一天
Didn't expect it to be so soon
没想到这么快
people must learn
人们必须学习
face everything
面对一切事情
During this period
在此期间
After escaping this mission
逃离这次任务后
I will do my best to protect you
我会尽全力保护你
What conditions?
什么条件？
Give me the card
把卡给我
Now that you have decided
既然你决定了
Leave Tianhai
离开天海
Why don't we go into the night fog?
我们为什么不进入夜雾呢？
be my partner
成为我的伙伴
right now we
我们现在
we are in the same boat
我们在同一条船上
Does it matter?
这重要吗？
don't you believe me
难道你不相信我
you do not trust me
你不信任我
This is my last paper
这是我的最后一篇论文
I won't give it to anyone
我不会把它给任何人
OK
好的
take it
拿去
When will the ship arrive?
船什么时候到？
Hello brother Zhang
张弟兄你好
OK
好的
Send me the website
把网站发给我
let's go
我们走吧
any ship
任何船舶
Is it Brother Zhang’s boat?
是张哥的船吗？
Yes
是的
Brother Zhang
张弟兄
come over
过来
Gentlemen
先生们
they hide inside
他们躲在里面
when the ship arrives
当船到达时
we will tell you
我们会告诉你
let's go
我们走吧
you made a wrong decision
你做了一个错误的决定
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Haven't you thought about it before?
你之前没想过吗？
Even if you give the data to Lao Yu
就算你把数据给老于
He won't trust you
他不会信任你
Know
知道
Do you still want to go?
你还想去吗？
I will stay in Tianhai
我会留在天海
This is a prison
这是监狱
go out
出去
At least I still have a way to live
至少我还有活路
Do you think
你认为
Can we escape this disaster?
我们能逃脱这场灾难吗？
at this time
此时
What scares me?
什么让我害怕？
correct
正确的
When I get used to constantly abandoning you
当我习惯了不断抛弃你
constantly changing location
不断改变位置
change identity
改变身份
Keep hiding
不断隐藏
this is amazing
这真太了不起了
This will be a normal meal
这将是一顿正常的饭菜
If I give you another chance
如果我再给你一次机会
Will you choose this path?
你会选择这条路吗？
I mean
我是说
become a spy
成为一名间谍
I never chose
我从来没有选择过
after she left
她离开后
do you think they are
你认为他们是
it disappointed me
让我失望
so
所以
You'd better not worry
你最好别担心
gay
同性恋
alone
独自的
you alone
你独自一人
you are in control
你尽在掌控
It seems so
看来是这样
after you tell me those stories
当你告诉我那些故事之后
I was just thinking
我刚在想
This is because
这是因为
your experience at that time
你当时的经历
Makes you think about a lot of things
让你思考了很多事情
on many things
在很多事情上
in this world
在这世上
It's not just you who dies
死去的不只是你
but i'm still alive
但我还活着
Humans have never
人类不曾
Depends on hurting others
取决于伤害别人
in order to survive
为了活下去
you really shouldn't
你真的不应该
leave with me
和我一起离开
Why
为什么
Mr. Yu asked you to do this
于先生要求你这样做
It seems that Night Mist and Empire
看来夜雾与帝国
they won't let me
他们不让我
Aren't you warning me too?
你不是也在警告我吗？
Give me the card
把卡给我
impossible
不可能的
I will send data
我将发送数据
If the verification is true
如果验证属实
We still have a chance to survive
我们还有机会活下去
No
不
Occasionally
偶尔
I think you are cruel
我觉得你很残忍
I think you are naive
我觉得你很天真
Have you ever thought about it?
你有没有想过？
Why did they let you?
他们为什么让你？
send data
发送数据
Obviously people and cards
显然人和卡
we can get back together
我们可以重归于好
my mission
我的使命
He got the card
他拿到卡
I will kill you
我会杀了你
So even if
所以即使
you will come back with me
你会和我一起回来
you can't live
你无法活下去
You now have a choice
你现在有一个选择
Give me the card
把卡给我
You can disembark now
你可以下船了
if you say so
如果你这么说
I can destroy this card
我可以毁掉这张卡
None of you understand
你们谁都不懂
I tell you the truth
我告诉你真相
we are just bait
我们只是诱饵
to attract
为了吸引
Attention National Security Office
国家安全办公室注意
another line
另一条线
this is a big fish
这是一条大鱼
You are Mr. Zhang
你是张先生
You are also bait
你也是诱饵
I
我
after i leave
我离开后
It will be replaced in a minute
一分钟后就会更换
Located in Tianhai
位于天海
Who has this ability?
谁有这个能力？
even if you are strong
即使你很坚强
I just
我只是
private worker games
私营工人游戏
As for that person
至于那个人
he is the real king
他是真正的国王
real king
真正的国王
Mr Z
Z先生
do you know him?
你认识他吗？
Who is Mr. Z?
Z先生是谁？
"Gao Tianyang."
“高天阳。”
She never rebelled
她从不叛逆
Yes or no?
是不是？
actually i was thinking
其实我在想
no plan at all
根本没有计划
leave with me
和我一起离开
The reason why you accompany me to the end
你陪我走到最后的理由
I just want to
只是想
Start from my mouth
从我嘴里说起
Why are you still stirring up trouble?
你为什么还在搅局？
I'm the bait
我是诱饵
i tell
我告诉
I never chose
我从来没有选择过
hope you have a chance
希望你有机会
Select again
再次选择
Mr. Zhang
张先生
haven't seen you for a long time
好久不见
Hello.
你好。
You're welcome
不客气
return
回来
Calling the night mist
呼唤夜雾
Was it eliminated?
被淘汰了吗？
No.
不。
senior police officer
高警官
I've let you down, Mr. Tony.
我让你失望了，托尼先生
I'm alive
我还活着
What will happen?
会怎么样呢？
Maybe there is a misunderstanding
或许有误会
When I let Jiahui kill me
当我让嘉慧杀了我的时候
never thought about it
从来没有想过
Explain this misunderstanding to me
给我解释一下这个误会
maybe she is wrong
也许她错了
we put in a lot of effort
我们付出了很多努力
to get you back
为了让你回来
Of course this won't happen
当然这不会发生
you
你们
You are good at justifying liability
你很擅长证明责任的合理性
But since Jiahui wants to kill me
但既然佳慧要杀我
I won't leave her
我不会离开她
This is normal
这个是正常的
this world
这个世界
You will always be the weak one
你永远都是弱者
our trip
我们的旅行
he will come to pick you up
他会来接你
I'm looking forward to meeting you
我期待着与您见面
no need
没有必要
I have arrived
我到了
you will get rid of me too
你也会摆脱我
if you don't come to us
如果你不来找我们
you have no better choice
你没有更好的选择
I will surrender myself
我会投降我自己
I admit?
我承认？
She did this to save Huang Ziqing
她这样做是为了救黄子晴
To save Huang Ziqing
为了救黄子晴
I will bring Mr. Zhang here now
现在我就带张先生来
surrender
投降
I think I can survive.
我想我能活下去。
senior police officer
高警官
Don't get emotional
不要情绪激动
we can talk
我们可以谈
No need to speak
无需说话
you betrayed me
你背叛了我
I won't let you live in peace
我不会让你平静地生活
it seems
它似乎
They don't care about your life or death
他们不关心你的生死
keep going
继续前进
you have to keep it
你必须保留它
They hung up.
他们挂断了电话。
but our trip
但我们的旅行
They were not received.
他们没有被收到。
Looks like they won't come back
看来他们不会回来了
We have another line
我们还有另一条线
you must leave immediately
你必须立即走
Accept Yaoyao
接收瑶瑶
Make sure there are no errors
确保没有错误
Understood
明白了
From the beginning
从一开始
The night fog has not completely dissipated yet
夜雾还没有完全消散
From the Office of National Security
来自国家安全办公室
I'm leaving the National Security Office
我要离开国家安全办公室
To them
对他们来说
worthless
一文不值
So people who enter it
所以进入其中的人
not you
不是你
But yaw yaw
但偏航偏航
Yes
是的
Do you trust her that much?
你就这么信任她吗？
i have never done this before
我以前从未这样做过
I checked Yaoyao’s order
我查了瑶瑶的订单
Since you started the game with a special mission
自从你带着特殊任务开始游戏
Everything related to night fog
一切与夜雾有关的事物
In principle
原则上
no difference
没有区别
Where is her sister Yao Yue?
她的妹妹姚月呢
I checked
我查了一下
This person already exists
此人已经存在
As Yaoyao said, the experience
正如瑶瑶所说的经历
Do you have any opinion
你有什么意见
Yaoyao helped us
瑶瑶帮助了我们
Complete the mission of killing Xiao Yi
完成杀死萧毅的使命
will have a greater impact in the future
未来将会产生更大的影响
If possible, Yaoyao
如果可以的话瑶瑶
for our work
为了我们的工作
this is very useful
这非常有用
in our work
在我们的工作中
Yes
是的
after this incident
这件事情之后
for night fog
对于夜雾
useless
无用
except me
除了我
Even if Xiao Yi is eliminated
就算萧毅被淘汰了
Yewu doesn't believe me easily
夜雾不轻易相信我
But Yaoyao is different
但瑶瑶不一样
She killed Xiao Yi with her own hands
她亲手杀了萧毅
From now on the night fog
从此夜雾
I will trust her more
我会更加信任她
Opposite of Yaoyao
与瑶瑶相反
It's really good for us
对我们确实是有好处的
But Yaoyao failed the test
但瑶瑶没有通过考验
Her attitude may waver
她的态度可能会动摇
also
此外
Her relationship with Huang Ziqing
她和黄子晴的关系
perhaps
或许
What you can't control
你无法控制的
Understood
明白了
Yaoyao is indeed a Lu sword
瑶瑶确实是一把吕剑
but i have confidence
但我有信心
To make good use of it
要想用好它
OK
好的
from now on
今后
Contact Yao Yao directly
专线联系姚姚
Yaoyao's identity
瑶瑶的身份
Not everyone can
不是每个人都可以
unplanned
计划之外
In addition, you must strengthen yourself through Yaoyao training
另外，一定要通过瑶瑶训练来增强自己
during exam
考试期间
and use with caution
并谨慎使用
Understood.
明白了。
Chu Zhe started
楚哲开始了
he suspects something
他怀疑某件事
We can move anytime
我们可以随时搬家
we have arrangements
我们有安排
your current mission
你现在的使命
he gained his trust
他得到了他的信任
Do not reveal your identity
不要透露您的身份
Understood
明白了
Why
为什么
She left with Mr. Zhang
她和张先生一起离开
We can't let Mr. Zhang go
我们不能放过张先生
The best way
最好的办法
He arrested me and Mr. Zhang
他把我和张先生抓了起来
Only in this way
只有这样
Yaoyao Night Mist can be turned on
瑶瑶夜雾可以开启
Let her return to Yewu headquarters
让她回到夜雾总部
so you can join
所以你可以加入
Can Yaoyao complete the mission?
瑶瑶能完成任务吗
She's not as weak as you think
她并不像你想象的那么弱
It's raining
下雨了
her training
她的训练
she is the best
她是最棒的
He hid her identity
他隐藏了她的身份
Where is Zicheng?
子成呢？
Why did you bring him here?
你为什么带他来这里？
The night mist entered his body
夜雾进入了他的体内
nature
自然
He chose it himself
他自己选择的
I don’t know how Tianyang is doing now
不知道天阳现在怎么样了
Zicheng
子成
if all this
如果这一切
Just a game
只是个游戏
this is amazing
这真太了不起了
Who are you
你是
Don't want to leave?
不想离开？
No
不
I just think
我只是想
All this is untrue
这一切都是不真实的
like
喜欢
unknown hand
未知的手
step by step to reach today
一步步走到今天
We really don't have time to give up now
我们现在真的没有时间放弃
too late
太晚了
we should move on
我们应该继续前进
yaw yaw
偏航 偏航
we will succeed
我们会成功
Believe me
相信我
i want a bottle of beer
我想要一瓶啤酒
i will bring it to you
我会把它带给你
for you
给你
when are you leaving?
你什么时候走？